Guide to the Department of Astronomy, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1860-1972; Accession 1977-A-001
  - III. Ernest William Brown, 1880-1939
    - Research notes
      - SD 16 Prelim, papers, Latitude D.E., undated (Box 26, Folder 164)
      - undated (Box 27, Folder 165-170)
      - Var. Art. Const. Methods, Reo see, December 1928 (Box 27, Folder 171)
      - Occultations Miscellaneous, 1933-1934 (Box 27, Folder 172)
      - Data for Tables of Remainder Terms (Box 27, Folder 173)
      - New Cal. for p series, 1930-1931 (Box 27, Folder 174)
      - Terms in l, 3l, 5l (Long) Long cycle plan and prelim. combined S 1 (S 1+S 1) continue with 2l 6l=S 1' and put in #1 which is not yet in any table, undated (Box 28, Folder 175)
      - undated (Box 28, Folder 176)
      - Periods and preliminary work, 1909 (Box 28, Folder 177)
      - undated (Box 28, Folder 178)
      - Useless attempts at the same m, a/a, undated (Box 28, Folder 179)
      - Working of the numerical and algebraic equations depending on m and a/a, undated (Box 28, Folder 180)
      - undated (Box 28, Folder 181)
      - 1 Drafts, undated (Box 28, Folder 182)
      - 3, undated (Box 28, Folder 183)
      - Terms in 2l, Long cycle plan, S 1' (50h), undated (Box 28, Folder 184)
      - undated (Box 28, Folder 185)
      - Calculations of P for Rene outer series, undated (Box 28, Folder 186)
      - undated (Box 28, Folder 187)
      - Functions (i, s) p=-.2, -.1, 0, .1,2, …2.5 s=1/2, 3/2, 5/2, undated (Box 28, Folder 188)
      - Numerical Values g (i/s) p=-.2, -.1, 0, .1, .2, …2.5 s=1/2, 3/2, 5/2, undated (Box 28, Folder 189)
      - Interpolation, undated (Box 28, Folder 190)
      - undated (Box 28, Folder 191)
      - Printed material, 1925, 1937-1938 (Box 28, Folder 192)
      - Occultations lists, 1933 (Box 28, Folder 193)
      - Occultations material, 1933 (Box 29, Folder 194)
      - Occultations observed, 1933 (Box 29, Folder 195)
      - Occultations tables A and B, 1933 (Box 29, Folder 196)
      - Occultation material, 1933-1939 (Box 29, Folder 197)
      - Occultations list, 1936 (Box 29, Folder 198)
      - Reduction of Occultation, Formulae of lunes, 1929-1937 (Box 30, Folder 199-201)
      - Reduction of Occultation, Formulae of lunes, 1929-1937 (Box 31, Folder 202-205)
      - Moon Tables, 1913 (Box 31, Folder 206)
      - Unknown periods, undated (Box 32, Folder 207)
      - Mathematical sem. Latitude {mean cos F and Sin F} Tab. Cor. us, undated (Box 32, Folder 208)
      - "The Transformation of the Moon's Latitude", 1911 (Box 32, Folder 209)
      - Trans. of lat. to long. to RA and Decl., done Feb 25, 1915, undated (Box 32, Folder 210)
      - Mean latitude, undated (Box 32, Folder 211)
      - Parallax of Moon by Observation, undated (Box 32, Folder 212)
      - Periodogram, 1924-1926 (Box 32, Folder 213)
      - Suggestions, 1917-1919 (Box 32, Folder 214)
      - # Terms Tabular, Hansem and Brown, undated (Box 32, Folder 215)
      - Mean Motion and Emp. Terms Discussion Hypotheses, undated (Box 32, Folder 216)
      - Possible Forces on Moon, 1912 (Box 32, Folder 217)
      - Latitude {mean cos F and sin F} Obs e Cor us, undated (Box 32, Folder 218)
      - Various old stuff; Trans. frat to tables and det n of counts, undated (Box 32, Folder 219)
      - undated (Box 32, Folder 220)
      - Russell moon photos, 1913-1917 (Box 32, Folder 221)
      - Cfn Gr-Harr Moon, 1911-1917 (Box 33, Folder 222)
      - Notebook, undated (Box 33, Folder 223)
      - undated (Box 33, Folder 224-225)
      - Chapter V Applic., undated (Box 33, Folder 226)
      - 1923-1924 (Box 33, Folder 227-228)
      - 4th order, Lat. dev., Int. orbit, undated (Box 33, Folder 229)
      - Achilles, 1923 (Box 33, Folder 230)
      - D 6, Returned May 1 st, Still to be interpolated to halves, undated (Box 33, Folder 231)
    - Miscellaneous Papers
      - Alg. and Trig., undated (Box 34, Folder 232)
      - Calculation print-outs, undated (Box 34, Folder 233)
      - Examination Papers, Cambridge University
        - 1880-1890 (Box 34, Folder 234)
      - 1887-1891, 1887-1897 (Box 34, Folder 235-236)
      - Examination Papers, other schools, 1891, 1905 (Box 34, Folder 237)
      - Maps, undated (Box 34, Folder 238)
      - Photograph - American Astronomical Society, 1923 (Box 34, Folder 239)
      - Problem Sets (printed), undated (Box 34, Folder 240)
      - Reprints
        - A-F, 1890-1935 (Box 35, Folder 241)
        - G-Ma, 1915-1935, undated (Box 35, Folder 242)
        - Me-Sch, 1901-1937, undated (Box 35, Folder 243)
        - Si-Z, 1902-1937, undated (Box 35, Folder 244)
        - Brown - 1925 (Box 35, Folder 245)
      - Tables, undated (Box 35, Folder 246)
    - Lectures
      - Calculus notebook, research notes (Celestial Mechanics lectures?), undated (Box 35a, Folder 247)
      - Celestial Mechanics, undated, 1907-1924. (Box 35a, Folder 248-251)
      - Per. Orbits (Celestial Mechanics), 1913-1914 (Box 35a, Folder 252)
      - Poincaré, undated (Box 35a, Folder 253)
  - IV. Frank Schlesinger, 1915-1952
    - Abbott, C.G., 1921-1940 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Abetti, Giorgio, 1924-1934 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Aca-Adams, C.H., 1920-1934 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Adams, Walter S., 1920-1942 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Ade-Agu, 1926-1941 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Aitken, Robert G., 1921-1941 (Box 36, Folder 6-8)
    - Allrecht, Sebastian, 1921-1927 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Alden, Harold L., 1920-1923, 1925-1928 (Box 36, Folder 10-14)
    - Alden, Harold L., 1929-1942 (Box 37, Folder 15-25)
    - Alg-All, 1923-1934 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Alter, Dinsmore, 1920-1939 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Alu-Ame, 1924-1942 (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - And-Arn, 1920-1938 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Art-Association, 1929-1941 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Astronomical-Astronomische, 1921-1942 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - At-Auckland, 1923-1940 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Bab-Baker, 1921-1938 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    - Baker, Robert H., 1921-1937 (Box 38, Folder 34)
    - Baker, S.-Ball, 1924-1935 (Box 38, Folder 35)
    - Banachiewicz, Th., 1923-1938 (Box 38, Folder 36)
    - Bann-Barnard, E.E., 1919-1920 (Box 38, Folder 37)
    - Barnard, E.E., 1921-1922 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Barnes-Bas, 1922-1934 (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Bauer-Louis E. (Carnegie Institute), 1920-1922 (Box 38, Folder 40)
    - Bausch and Lomb Optical Company, 1927-1933 (Box 38, Folder 41)
    - Bauschi-Baxter, 1921-1941 (Box 38, Folder 42)
    - Bea-Bee, 1920-1935 (Box 38, Folder 43)
    - Beer, Arthur, 1928-1941 (Box 38, Folder 44)
    - Begg-Bell, 1921-1935 (Box 38, Folder 45)
    - Belopolsky, A., 1922 (Box 38, Folder 46)
    - Bem-Benh, 1926-1934 (Box 38, Folder 47)
    - Bennett, Arthur L., 1931-1941 (Box 38, Folder 48)
    - Bennett-Ber, 1921-1941 (Box 38, Folder 49)
    - Bha-Bil, 1921-1942 (Box 38, Folder 50)
    - Bin-Bon, 1922-1942 (Box 39, Folder 51)
    - Boo-Bosl, 1920-1941 (Box 39, Folder 52)
    - Van den Bos, W.H., 1927-1942 (Box 39, Folder 53)
    - Boss, Benjamin, 1919-1942 (Box 39, Folder 54-56)
    - Bourgeois, P.-Bowie, William, 1922-1923 (Box 39, Folder 57)
    - Bowie, William, 1924-1936 (Box 39, Folder 58-59)
    - Bowm-Brasch, Frederick E. (Box 39, Folder 60)
    - Bashear Company (James B. McDowell), 1920-1921 (Box 39, Folder 61)
    - Bran-Brooks, 1919-1942 (Box 39, Folder 62)
    - Brouwer, Dick, 1927-1928, 1933-1940 (Box 39, Folder 63-64)
    - Brown and Sharp Company, 1923-1934 (Box 39, Folder 65)
    - Brown, Ernest W., 1915-1937 (Box 39, Folder 66)
    - Brown, J.-Burnh, 1922-1942 (Box 39, Folder 67)
    - Burns, Keivin, 1920-1942 (Box 40, Folder 68)
    - Bursary Appointments, 1935-1942 (Box 40, Folder 69)
    - Burt-Bus, 1922-1942 (Box 40, Folder 70)
    - Cad-Campbell, Leon, 1921-1933 (Box 40, Folder 71)
    - Campbell, W.W., 1920-1937 (Box 40, Folder 72)
    - Cannon, Annie J.-Cannon, C.L., 1921-1939 (Box 40, Folder 73)
    - Carnegie Institution, 1932-1942 (Box 40, Folder 74)
    - Carp-Cath, 1933-1938 (Box 40, Folder 75)
    - Cattell, J. McKeen, 1919-1936 (Box 40, Folder 76)
    - Cec-Chan, 1920-1938 (Box 40, Folder 77)
    - Char-Chr, 1920-1939 (Box 40, Folder 78)
    - Alvan Clark and Sons Corporation, 1920-1929 (Box 40, Folder 79)
    - Clarke-Cloos, 1927-1942 (Box 40, Folder 80)
    - Coa-Coll, 1921-1941 (Box 40, Folder 81)
    - Columbia L.-Columbia University, 1919-1935 (Box 40, Folder 82)
    - Coma-Comp, 1924-1936 (Box 40, Folder 83)
    - Comrie, L.J., 1922-1940 (Box 40, Folder 84-85)
    - Coms-Cook, 1927-1929 (Box 41, Folder 86)
    - Cooke, W. Ernest, 1920-1932 (Box 41, Folder 87)
    - Cooks-Cox, 1921-1941 (Box 41, Folder 88)
    - Cra-Cross, 1922-1942 (Box 41, Folder 89)
    - Cross-Whitman, 1921-1927 (Box 41, Folder 90)
    - Cross, Wilber-Curr, 1922-1941 (Box 41, Folder 91)
    - Curtis, Herber D., 1920-1940 (Box 41, Folder 92-93)
    - Curtiss, R.H.-Cus, 1923-1929 (Box 41, Folder 95)
    - Daghlian, G.K., 1926-1934 (Box 41, Folder 96)
    - Dal-David, 1921-1938 (Box 41, Folder 97)
    - Davis, H.T.-Day, 1915-1936 (Box 41, Folder 98)
    - Davis, Charles H., 1922-1931 (Box 41, Folder 99)
    - Davis, F.-Davis, George A, 1927-1941 (Box 41, Folder 100)
    - Def-Delporte, 1928-1929 (Box 41, Folder 101)
    - Den-Der, 1927-1937 (Box 41, Folder 102)
    - DeSitter, Willem, 1922-1935 (Box 41, Folder 103-105)
    - Desl-Dev, 1928-1939 (Box 41, Folder 106)
    - Dim-Don, 1923-1942 (Box 41, Folder 107)
    - Doo-Dou, 1920-1926 (Box 42, Folder 108)
    - Dra-Duf, 1921-1942 (Box 42, Folder 109)
    - Dugan, Raymond S., 1920-1937 (Box 42, Folder 110-111)
    - Dugan, Stephen P., 1932-1939 (Box 42, Folder 112)
    - Dun-Dus, 1923-1938 (Box 42, Folder 113)
    - Dyson, Frank Watson, 1920-1935 (Box 42, Folder 114)
    - Dzi-Eastman Kodak Co., 1928-1942 (Box 42, Folder 115)
    - Eat-Ebe, 1922-1942 (Box 42, Folder 116)
    - Eckert, Wallace J., 1926-1942 (Box 42, Folder 117-118)
    - Eclipse, 1923, 1932 (Box 42, Folder 119-120)
    - EDD-Eff, 1928-1940 (Box 42, Folder 121)
    - Eichelberger, W.S., 1921-1929 (Box 42, Folder 122)
    - Ein-Elk, 1928-1942 (Box 42, Folder 123)
    - Eme-Exi, 1932-1942 (Box 42, Folder 124)
    - Fab-Farnam, Thomas W., 1923-1933 (Box 42, Folder 125)
    - Farns-Fay, 1923-1942 (Box 42, Folder 126)
    - Fecker, J.W., 1923-1936 (Box 42, Folder 127)
    - Fed-Fel, 1941-1942 (Box 42, Folder 128)
    - Fener, Roy Y., 1922-1934 (Box 42, Folder 129)
    - Fil-Fisher, 1924-1935 (Box 42, Folder 130)
    - Fish-Schurman-For, 1932-1941 (Box 42, Folder 131)
    - Fou-Fow, 1920-1934 (Box 43, Folder 132)
    - Fox, Philip, 1920-1940 (Box 43, Folder 133-134)
    - Foy-Fri, 1926-1938 (Box 43, Folder 135)
    - Frost, Edwin B., 1920-1932 (Box 43, Folder 136)
    - Ful-Furness, Caroline E., 1920-1936 (Box 43, Folder 137)
    - Gaertner, William, 1920-1926 (Box 43, Folder 138-139)
    - Gag-Gal (Box 43, Folder 140)
    - Gam-Gav, 1936-1942 (Box 43, Folder 141)
    - Gen-Geo, 1928-1934 (Box 43, Folder 142)
    - Ger-Ges, 1927-1938 (Box 43, Folder 143)
    - Gibbs, F.H., 1916-1924 (Box 43, Folder 144)
    - Gibbs, Gin, 1927-1942 (Box 43, Folder 145)
    - Glass disk, 1923-1924 (Box 43, Folder 146)
    - God-Graa, 1923-1940 (Box 43, Folder 147)
    - Graduate School, 1923-1942 (Box 43, Folder 148)
    - Graf-Green, L.C., 1923-1938 (Box 43, Folder 149)
    - Green, Warren K., 1924-1934 (Box 43, Folder 150)
    - Gre-Gut, 1923-1938 (Box 43, Folder 151)
    - Haa-Halb, 1921-1938 (Box 44, Folder 152)
    - Hale, George E, 1920-1935 (Box 44, Folder 153)
    - Hall, C.-Hall G., 1924-1941 (Box 44, Folder 154)
    - Hall, John S., 1931-1939 (Box 44, Folder 155)
    - Halm-Har, 1923-1939 (Box 44, Folder 156)
    - Has-Hau, 1911-1930 (Box 44, Folder 157)
    - Hav-Hed, 1922-1942 (Box 44, Folder 158)
    - Hellweg, J.F., 1930-1942 (Box 44, Folder 159)
    - Hen-Hep, 1924-1926 (Box 44, Folder 160)
    - Herget, Paul, 1935-1942 (Box 44, Folder 161)
    - Herr, 1929-1934 (Box 44, Folder 162)
    - Hertz, Hans, 1936-1937 (Box 44, Folder 163)
    - Hertzsprumg, Ejnar, 1926-1941 (Box 44, Folder 164)
    - Hes-Hin, 1922-1942 (Box 44, Folder 165)
    - Her-Hol, 1923-1942 (Box 44, Folder 166)
    - Hoo-Hum, 1924-1939 (Box 44, Folder 167)
    - Hun-Hyn, 1920-1936 (Box 44, Folder 168)
    - Il-Ing, 1931-1936 (Box 44, Folder 169)
    - Innes, R.T.A., 1923-1929 (Box 44, Folder 170-171)
    - Ins-Internal, 1933-1934 (Box 44, Folder 172)
    - International Astronomical Union, 1924-1937 (Box 45, Folder 173-175)
    - International Business-Isd, 1928-1940 (Box 45, Folder 176)
    - Jack-Jackson, J., 1923-1942 (Box 45, Folder 177)
    - Jackson, M-Jea, 1920-1936 (Box 45, Folder 178)
    - Jeffers, Hamilton M., 1927-1936 (Box 45, Folder 179)
    - Jeffr-Jones, F., 1933-1937 (Box 45, Folder 180)
    - Jones, H. Spencer, 1924-1942 (Box 45, Folder 181)
    - Jordan, Frank C., 1920-1939 (Box 45, Folder 182)
    - Jordan, H.-Joy, 1920-1931 (Box 45, Folder 183)
    - Kae-Kah, 1932-1933 (Box 45, Folder 184)
    - van de Kamp, Peter, 1926-1941 (Box 45, Folder 185)
    - Kap-Kie, 1920-1942 (Box 45, Folder 186)
    - Kimura, H., 1921-1941 (Box 46, Folder 187)
    - Kin-Kis, 1921-1935 (Box 46, Folder 188)
    - Klages, George W., 1920-1924 (Box 46, Folder 189)
    - Kle-Knopf, 1920-1941 (Box 46, Folder 190)
    - Knox-Shaw, H.-Koh, 1923-1935 (Box 46, Folder 191)
    - Kopff, A., 1926-1937 (Box 46, Folder 192)
    - Kow-Kyl, 1925-1942 (Box 46, Folder 193)
    - Lab-Lai, 1928-1944 (Box 46, Folder 194)
    - Lambert, Walter D., 1921-1942 (Box 46, Folder 195)
    - Lamp-Lan, 1929-1941 (Box 46, Folder 196)
    - Latitude, Joint Commission on The Variation of, 1920-1937 (Box 46, Folder 197)
    - Lav-Lee, M., 1923-1942 (Box 46, Folder 198)
    - Lee, Oliver J., 1920-1941 (Box 46, Folder 199)
    - Leeds and Northrup Company, 1929-1933 (Box 46, Folder 200)
    - Leh-Leonard, C., 1924-1931 (Box 46, Folder 201)
    - Leonard, Frederick C., 1925-1938 (Box 46, Folder 202)
    - Leuschner, A.O., 1920-1942 (Box 46, Folder 203)
    - Lew-Libb, 1924-1929 (Box 46, Folder 204)
    - Library, Yale University, 1925-1942 (Box 46, Folder 205)
    - Lil-Lul, 1920-1941 (Box 47, Folder 206)
    - Lun-Lut, 1922-1937 (Box 47, Folder 207)
    - Luyten, William J., 1923-1939 (Box 47, Folder 208)
    - Ly, 1925-1938 (Box 47, Folder 209)
    - van Maanen, Adriaan, 1920-1942 (Box 47, Folder 210)
    - McC, 1920-1942 (Box 47, Folder 211)
    - McDowell, James B., 1921-1922 (Box 47, Folder 212-214)
    - McF-McM, 1920-1942 (Box 47, Folder 215)
    - Mec-Mel, 1920-1938 (Box 47, Folder 216)
    - Mehlin, Theodore G., 1932-1942 (Box 47, Folder 217)
    - Men-Mil, 1919-1941 (Box 47, Folder 218)
    - Mersick, C.S. and Company, 1928-1937 (Box 47, Folder 219)
    - Miller, John A., 1920-1937 (Box 47, Folder 220)
    - Mitchell, S.A., 1915-1941 (Box 48, Folder 221-222)
    - Moe-Murphy, 1927-1940 (Box 48, Folder 223)
    - Morgan, H.R., 1930-1932 (Box 48, Folder 224)
    - Moulton, F.R., 1921-1943 (Box 48, Folder 225)
    - Nag-National Academy of Science, 1921-1942 (Box 48, Folder 226-227)
    - National B-National C, 1929-1937 (Box 48, Folder 228)
    - National Research Council, 1921-1942 (Box 48, Folder 229)
    - National Research Council: Revision of Statutes, International Research Council, 1928-1929 (Box 48, Folder 230)
    - National Research Fund, 1928 (Box 48, Folder 231)
    - Nat-Nautical Almanac Office, 1938-1939 (Box 48, Folder 232)
    - Naval Observatory, 1927-1936 (Box 48, Folder 233)
    - Nay-Neg, 1927-1940 (Box 48, Folder 234)
    - "Neighbors," The, 1924-1952 (Box 48, Folder 235)
    - Nel-Newt, 1923-1942 (Box 49, Folder 236)
    - New Zeland, 1920-1923 (Box 49, Folder 237-238)
    - Nisoli, Franze, 1933-1939 (Box 49, Folder 239)
    - Nis-Nor, 1926-1940 (Box 49, Folder 240)
    - Norstrand, D. Van Company, Inc., 1928-1938 (Box 49, Folder 241)
    - Numerov, B.V., 1929-1936 (Box 49, Folder 242)
    - Obr-Obs, 1929-1942 (Box 49, Folder 243)
    - Observatory, Yale, 1918-1919 (Box 49, Folder 244)
    - O'Connell, Walter, 1925-1940 (Box 49, Folder 245)
    - Og-Ole, 1921-1942 (Box 49, Folder 246)
    - Oliver, Charles P., 1920-1938 (Box 49, Folder 247)
    - Oort, Jan H., 1922-1940 (Box 49, Folder 248)
    - Op-Orders for Bright Stars Catalogue, 1931 (Box 49, Folder 249)
    - Os-Oy, 1923-1940 (Box 49, Folder 250)
    - Pad-Pan, 1933-1937 (Box 49, Folder 251)
    - Parallax, 1921-1933 (Box 49, Folder 252)
    - Parr-Peg, 1922-1940 (Box 50, Folder 253)
    - Penniman, Josiah H., 1920-1928 (Box 50, Folder 254)
    - Pere, 1941-1942 (Box 50, Folder 255)
    - Periodicals, 1929 (Box 50, Folder 256)
    - Perrier, G., 1924-1934 (Box 50, Folder 257)
    - Perrine, Charles D., 1924-1939 (Box 50, Folder 258-259)
    - Perry-Petti, 1920-1942 (Box 50, Folder 260)
    - Petty Cash, 1932-1936 (Box 50, Folder 261)
    - Ph-Phi, 1924-1938 (Box 50, Folder 262)
    - Photographic reproduction of catalogue, 1932-1933 (Box 50, Folder 263)
    - Pi, 1920-1942 (Box 50, Folder 264)
    - Plaskett, Henry (Harry) H., 1927-1937 (Box 50, Folder 265)
    - Plaskett, J.S., 1920-1932 (Box 50, Folder 266)
    - Plu-Po, 1915-1935 (Box 50, Folder 267)
    - Prager, Richard, 1926-1937 (Box 50, Folder 268)
    - Prager-Presc, 1926-1933 (Box 50, Folder 269)
    - President, Office of Yale University, 1929-1932 (Box 50, Folder 270-271)
    - Press-Provi, 1923-1937 (Box 50, Folder 272)
    - Provost, Office of Yale University, 1923-1943 (Box 50, Folder 273-274)
    - Prz-Pu, 1927-1933 (Box 50, Folder 275)
    - Q, 1929-1930 (Box 50, Folder 276)
    - Rad-Reu, 1924-1942 (Box 50, Folder 277)
    - van Rhÿn, P.J., 1922-1942 (Box 51, Folder 278)
    - Ric-Riv, 1925-1942 (Box 51, Folder 279)
    - Rob-Rol, 1923-1941 (Box 51, Folder 280)
    - Ros-Rosenbach, 1925-1933 (Box 51, Folder 281)
    - Rosenberg, Hans, 1933-1936 (Box 51, Folder 282)
    - Rosenberg, L.L.-Rosenthal, 1928-1932 (Box 51, Folder 283)
    - Ross, Frank E., 1920-1939 (Box 51, Folder 284)
    - Rossier-Rui, 1928-1941 (Box 51, Folder 285)
    - Russell, Henry Norris, 1920-1941 (Box 51, Folder 286-287)
    - Russell, W.H.-Ryb, 1932-1942 (Box 51, Folder 288)
    - Sadler, D.H., 1936-1941 (Box 51, Folder 289)
    - Sal-Saw, 1922-1934 (Box 51, Folder 290)
    - Schilt, Jan, 1926-1942 (Box 51, Folder 291-293)
    - Schlesinger, Frank, 1928, 1938-1942 (Box 52, Folder 294)
    - Schlesinger, Wagner, 1931-1940 (Box 52, Folder 295)
    - Schl-Sea, 1921-1942 (Box 52, Folder 296)
    - Secretary, office of, Yale University, 1920-1942 (Box 52, Folder 297-298)
    - Sed-Seg, 1923-1938 (Box 52, Folder 299)
    - Sellew, R.W., 1923-1929 (Box 52, Folder 300-301)
    - Sem, 1936 (Box 52, Folder 302)
    - Service Bureau, Yale University
      - Correspondence, 1927-1942 (Box 52, Folder 303)
      - Purchase orders, 1932-1933 (Box 52, Folder 304)
      - Statements and receipts, 1928-1933 (Box 52, Folder 305-306)
    - Sey, 1926-1937 (Box 52, Folder 307)
    - Shapley, Harlow, 1921-1928 (Box 52, Folder 308-309)
    - Shapley, Harlow, 1929-1942 (Box 53, Folder 310-311)
    - She-Sit, 1926-1941 (Box 53, Folder 312)
    - Sitt-Sk, 1932 (Box 53, Folder 313)
    - Slavenas, Paul, 1926-1935 (Box 53, Folder 314)
    - Sli, 1921-1935 (Box 53, Folder 315)
    - Slocum, Frederick, 1919-1939 (Box 53, Folder 316)
    - Sm-Som, 1921-1941 (Box 53, Folder 317)
    - South Africa, 1923-1941 (Box 53, Folder 318)
    - Sp-Steb, 1920-1941 (Box 53, Folder 319)
    - Stebbins, Joel, 1920-1942 (Box 53, Folder 320)
    - Stec-Ster, 1933-1942 (Box 53, Folder 321)
    - Stetson, Harlan T., 1925-1940 (Box 53, Folder 322)
    - Stew-Stod, 1922-1939 (Box 53, Folder 323)
    - Stokley, James, 1931-1938 (Box 53, Folder 324)
    - Stom-Strac, 1922-1941 (Box 53, Folder 325)
    - Stratton, F.J.M., 1926-1938 (Box 53, Folder 326)
    - Strat-Stro, 1920-1934 (Box 54, Folder 327)
    - Struve, Otto, 1926-1942 (Box 54, Folder 328)
    - Struve, Georg, 1926-1933 (Box 54, Folder 329)
    - Stu-Sy, 1922-1941 (Box 54, Folder 330)
    - Tab-Tho, 1920-1941 (Box 54, Folder 331)
    - Tic-Tread, 1920-1941 (Box 54, Folder 332)
    - Treasurer, Yale University
      - Correspondence, 1922-1942 (Box 54, Folder 333-336)
      - Pay slips, 1929-1933 (Box 54, Folder 337-338)
      - Remittance slips, 1936-1942 (Box 54, Folder 339-341)
    - Trowbridge, Augustus, 1920-1929 (Box 55, Folder 342)
    - Trumpler, Robert J., 1920-1937 (Box 55, Folder 343)
    - Tuc-Turner, 1921-1932 (Box 55, Folder 344)
    - Turner, Herbert H., 1921-1930 (Box 55, Folder 345)
    - Tut-Twy, 1929-1933 (Box 55, Folder 346)
    - Ue-Uni, 1924-1940 (Box 55, Folder 347)
    - Van-Vys, 1920-1942 (Box 55, Folder 348)
    - Wal-War, 1922-1939 (Box 55, Folder 349)
    - Warren, Charles H., 1929-1942 (Box 55, Folder 350)
    - Was-Wat, 1926-1942 (Box 55, Folder 351)
    - Web-Whitl, 1921-1942 (Box 55, Folder 352)
    - Whitworth, Ernest, 1930-1940 (Box 56, Folder 353)
    - Who-Will, 1926-1942 (Box 56, Folder 354)
    - Wilson, Edwin B., 1922-1932 (Box 56, Folder 355)
    - Wilson, Herbert C., H. W. Wilson, 1922-1926 (Box 56, Folder 356)
    - Wilson, Ralph E., 1926-1942 (Box 56, Folder 357)
    - Wilson, W.A.-Wol, 1920-1937 (Box 56, Folder 358)
    - Woo-Wyl, 1922-1942 (Box 56, Folder 359)
    - Yal-Yoa, 1920-1942 (Box 56, Folder 360)
    - Young, Anne S., 1924-1942 (Box 56, Folder 361)
    - Young, Reynold K., 1921-1922 (Box 56, Folder 362)
    - Zan-Zoo, 1923-1942 (Box 56, Folder 363)
    - Zug, R.S., 1935 (Box 56, Folder 364)
  - V. Dirk Brouwer, 1939-1967
    - Departmental correspondence
      - A, 1943-1960 (Box 57, Folder 1-5)
      - Abdala, Jose, 1961 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Academic Press, 1960-1964 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Alden, Harold L., 1943-1945 (Box 57, Folder 8-9)
      - Alumni Seminar (Alumni Board), 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1960 (Box 58, Folder 12)
      - American Association of Variable Star Observers, 1943-1946 (Box 58, Folder 13)
      - American Astronomical Society, 1945-1965 (Box 58, Folder 14-17)
      - American Geophysical Union Committee on Geodetic Applications and Artificial Satellites, 1958 (Box 58, Folder 18)
      - American Mathematical Society
        General
        See: box 73, folder 202
      - Applications for Grants, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 19)
      - Artificial satellites, 1960-1961 (Box 58, Folder 20)
      - Association of Universities for Research in Astronomy (AURA), 1957-1958, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 21)
      - Asteroid Ephemerides, 1946-1947 (Box 58, Folder 22)
      - Astrometry
        See: box 79, folder 260
      - Astrometry Conference, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 23)
      - Astronomical Discovery by Herbert Hall Turner, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 24)
      - Astronomical notes, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 25)
      - Astronomical Society of the Pacific, 1965 (Box 59, Folder 26)
      - B, 1943-1964 (Box 59, Folder 27-32)
      - Berkeley College, 1955-1960 (Box 59, Folder 33)
      - Bethany Observatory: Astrographic Telescope, 1961-1962 (Box 60, Folder 34)
      - Bethany Observatory construction, 1956-1957 (Box 60, Folder 35)
      - Bethany Observatory National Science Foundation grant, 1961-1963 (Box 60, Folder 36)
      - Bibliography, 1959-1960 (Box 60, Folder 37)
      - Bills, 1951-1959 (Box 60, Folder 38-39)
      - Bright Star Catalogue: Transactions of the Astronomical Observatory of Yale University: orders and invoices, 1958-1959 (Box 60, Folder 40)
      - Broucke, Roger, 1963 (Box 60, Folder 41)
      - Brouwer, Dirk, 1947-1958 (Box 60, Folder 42)
      - Brussels Conference, 1954-1956 (Box 60, Folder 43)
      - Building expansion, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 44)
      - Bursary, 1943-1962 (Box 60, Folder 45)
      - C, 1943-1965 (Box 61, Folder 46-50)
      - Carcus Conference, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 51)
      - Carnegie Institution, 1943-1946 (Box 61, Folder 52)